Baylor-Carrington Family papers, Inclusive: 1715-2007, undated, Bulk: 1840-1930
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Legal Documents, 1770-1907; 2
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1904 May 4-1907 June 27 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1907 July 8-1915 March 12 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Financial Documents, 1877-1915; 3
  This series consists of financial documents from the Carrington family, especially tax records from the late nineteenth century to the early twentieth century.
  - General: Carrington Family, 1877 January 1-1891 September 8 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Taxes: Carrington Family, 1876 May 2 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Taxes: Carrington Family, 1878 January 18-1915 January 30 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Literary Productions, 1844-2007; 4
  This series consists of printed materials, collected materials, subject files, genealogical materials, biographical materials, clippings, manuscripts, and other types of literary productions. Included are materials created by Baylor family members (like the many newspaper articles by George Wythe Baylor) as well as information about members of the family (like the many biographical and genealogical materials). While the series is generally in good condition, Addie DeLeon Hamer Baylor's materials are in poor condition.
  - Printed Materials: General, 1922, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Printed Materials: Deutsche Library, 1881 May 14 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Printed Materials: Deutsche Library, 1881 September 15 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Printed Materials: Deutsche Library, 1882 April 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials: “Draft of an Act to Prevent Corrupt Practices in General and Primary Elections”, 1896 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials: James Belger Baylor and Daniel C. Hazard: “General Report on the Magnetic Survey of North Carolina", 1900 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials: John E. McGrath: “The Transcontinental Triangulation and the American Arc of the Parallel”, 1901 January 3 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials: James Belger Baylor: “Education of the Masses in its Relation to Production”, 1903 April 20 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials: O.H. Tittman: “The Work of the United States and Geodetic Survey”, 1903 July (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials: Artemis Martin: “Prime Numbers in Arithmetical Progression”, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials: The Huisache, 1914 January-1919 May 23, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials: J.S. Plaskett: “W. F. King”, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials: Mrs. W.T. Lafferty: Pageant of Kentucky’s Historic Past, 1924 June 16 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials: The Baylor Monthly, 1930 April, May (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials: The Baylor Monthly, 1930 June, 1931 January (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials: The Baylor Monthly, 1931 May (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials: The Baylor Monthly, 1931 June, October (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Printed Materials: Baylor’s Quarterly Magazine of Family History (1 of 2), 1930 April (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials: Baylor’s Quarterly Magazine of Family History (2 of 2), 1930 April (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Printed Materials: Baylor’s Quarterly Magazine of Family History, 1930 July (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Printed Materials: Baylor’s Quarterly Magazine of Family History, 1930 October (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Printed Materials: Baylor’s Quarterly Magazine of Family History (1 of 2), 1931 January (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Printed Materials: Baylor’s Quarterly Magazine of Family History (2 of 2), 1931 January (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Printed Materials: Baylor’s Quarterly Magazine of Family History, 1931 July (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Printed Materials: Baylor’s Quarterly Magazine of Family History, 1931 October, 1932 January (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Printed Materials: Baylor’s Quarterly Magazine of Family History, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Printed Materials: Baylor’s Quarterly Magazine of Family History, 1932 April (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Printed Materials: The Baylor Century, 1938 November (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Printed Materials: The Baylor Century, 1938 December (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Printed Materials: The Baylor Century, 1939 January (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Printed Materials: The Baylor Century, 1942 January (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Printed Materials: The Baylor Century, 1942 February (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Printed Materials: The Baylor Century, 1945 January (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Printed Materials: James Henry Gardner: “The Lost Captain: J.L. Dawson of Old Fort Gibson”, 1943 September (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Printed Materials: Poetry: Dorothy Baylor: Reflections, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Printed Materials: C.F. William Maurer: “Just Passing Through”: George Baylor, 1978 September (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Printed Materials: Walker Keith Baylor: “Events of Long Ago”, 1931 May (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Printed Materials: Sheet Music: Stabat Mater de Rossini, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Printed Materials: The Baylorian, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials: George L. Willis, Sr.: Prospectus: History of Shelby County, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Collected Materials: General (1 of 4), 1844 February 4-1978 September, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Collected Materials: General (2 of 4), 1844 February 4-1978 September, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Collected Materials: General (3 of 4), 1844 February 4-1978 September, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Collected Materials: General (4 of 4), 1844 February 4-1978 September, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Collected Materials: Envelopes, 1844 August 12-1907 June 13, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Collected Materials: Travel Brochures, 1929-1931 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Collected Materials: Travel Brochures, 1931-1932 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Collected Materials: Travel Brochures, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Collected Materials: Travel Brochures (1 of 2), undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Collected Materials: Travel Brochures (2 of 2), undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Collected Materials: Christmas Cards, 1932 December 21, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Collected Materials: Postcards: Texas Centennial (1 of 2), 1936 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Collected Materials: Postcards: Texas Centennial (2 of 2), 1936 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Collected Materials: Postcards: General, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Collected Materials: Postcards: Washington, D.C., undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Collected Materials: Postcards: Virginia (1 of 3), undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Collected Materials: Postcards: Virginia (2 of 3), undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Collected Materials: Postcards: Virginia (3 of 3), undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Collected Materials: Postcards: Kentucky, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Collected Materials: Postcards: West Virginia, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Subject Files: Baylor and Allied Families Reunions (1 of 6), 1926 July 6-1940 February 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Subject Files: Baylor and Allied Families Reunions (2 of 6), 1926 July 6-1940 February 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Subject Files: Baylor and Allied Families Reunions (3 of 6), 1926 July 6-1940 February 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Subject Files: Baylor and Allied Families Reunions (4 of 6), 1926 July 6-1940 February 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Subject Files: Baylor and Allied Families Reunions (5 of 6), 1926 July 6-1940 February 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Subject Files: Baylor and Allied Families Reunions (6 of 6), 1926 July 6-1940 February 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Subject Files: Baylor University: General (1 of 4), 1936 May 29-1964 October 11, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Subject Files: Baylor University: General (2 of 4), 1936 May 29-1964 October 11, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Subject Files: Baylor University: General (3 of 4), 1936 May 29-1964 October 11, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Subject Files: Baylor University: General (4 of 4), 1936 May 29-1964 October 11, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Subject Files: Baylor University: 96th Commencement, 1941 June 2 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Subject Files: Baylor University: Centennial, 1945 February 1 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Subject Files: Texas History (1 of 4), 1935-1939 April (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Subject Files: Texas History (2 of 4), 1935-1939 April (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Subject Files: Texas History (3 of 4), 1935-1939 April (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Subject Files: Texas History (4 of 4), 1935-1939 April (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Subject Files: Clippings: Texas Revolution, 1936 March 27-1937 April 25 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Subject Files: Texas Centennial, 1936, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Subject Files: Clippings: Leon County, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Subject Files: Clippings: Civil War, 1943 March 14-1961 December 10 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Subject Files: Clippings: World War II, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Subject Files: Clippings: World War II Poetry, 1942 February 10, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Subject Files: Clippings: World War II Poetry, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Subject Files: John Nance Garner (1 of 2), 1936 June 26-1960 November 20, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Subject Files: John Nance Garner (2 of 2), 1936 June 26-1960 November 20, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Subject Files: Clippings: John Nance Garner, 1967 November 8, undated (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Genealogical Materials: General, undated (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Genealogical Materials: Baylor and Related Families (1 of 9), 1875-1978 September 29, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Genealogical Materials: Baylor and Related Families (2 of 9), 1875-1978 September 29, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Genealogical Materials: Baylor and Related Families (3 of 9), 1875-1978 September 29, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Genealogical Materials: Baylor and Related Families (4 of 9), 1875-1978 September 29, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Genealogical Materials: Baylor and Related Families (5 of 9), 1875-1978 September 29, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Genealogical Materials: Baylor and Related Families (6 of 9), 1875-1978 September 29, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Genealogical Materials: Baylor and Related Families (7 of 9), 1875-1978 September 29, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Genealogical Materials: Baylor and Related Families (8 of 9), 1875-1978 September 29, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Genealogical Materials: Baylor and Related Families (9 of 9), 1875-1978 September 29, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Genealogical Materials: Orval Walker Baylor and Henry Bedinger Baylor: Baylor’s History of the Baylors: Baylor Family (1 of 6), 1914 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Genealogical Materials: Orval Walker Baylor and Henry Bedinger Baylor: Baylor’s History of the Baylors: Baylor Family (2 of 6), 1914 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Genealogical Materials: Orval Walker Baylor and Henry Bedinger Baylor: Baylor’s History of the Baylors: Baylor Family (3 of 6), 1914 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Genealogical Materials: Orval Walker Baylor and Henry Bedinger Baylor: Baylor’s History of the Baylors: Baylor Family (4 of 6), 1914 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Genealogical Materials: Orval Walker Baylor and Henry Bedinger Baylor: Baylor’s History of the Baylors: Baylor Family (5 of 6), 1914 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Genealogical Materials: Orval Walker Baylor and Henry Bedinger Baylor: Baylor’s History of the Baylors: Baylor Family (6 of 6), 1914 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Genealogical Materials: Carrington Family (1 of 4), 1944 August 21, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Genealogical Materials: Carrington Family (2 of 4), 1944 August 21, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Genealogical Materials: Carrington Family (3 of 4), 1944 August 21, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Genealogical Materials: Carrington Family (4 of 4), 1944 August 21, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Genealogical Materials: Walker Family (1 of 2), 1801 February 7-1984 September 1 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Genealogical Materials: Walker Family (2 of 2), 1801 February 7-1984 September 1 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Genealogical Materials: Bayleur Coat of Arms, 1949 February 18, 1968 March 24, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Genealogical Materials: Baylor Family (1 of 2), undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Genealogical Materials: Baylor Family (2 of 2), undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Genealogical Materials: The Baylor Family of Newmarket: Copy 1 (1 of 2), undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Genealogical Materials: The Baylor Family of Newmarket: Copy 1 (2 of 2), undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Genealogical Materials: The Baylor Family of Newmarket: Copy 2 (1 of 2), undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Genealogical Materials: The Baylor Family of Newmarket: Copy 2 (2 of 2), undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Genealogical Materials: Walker Keith Baylor: “The Baylor Family” (1 of 2), undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Genealogical Materials: Walker Keith Baylor: “The Baylor Family” (2 of 2), undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Biographical Materials: Baylor Family, 1854 May 23-1886 February 16 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Biographical Materials: Baylor Family, 1952-1973 July 18 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Biographical Materials: Baylor Family, 1978 September-1979 April 16, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Biographical Materials: John Robert Baylor, 1866, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Biographical Materials: John Robert Baylor, 1921, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Biographical Materials: George Wythe Baylor: “Genl-John Robert Baylor of Texas” (1 of 5), 1900 December 25 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Biographical Materials: George Wythe Baylor: “Genl-John Robert Baylor of Texas” (2 of 5), 1900 December 25 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Biographical Materials: George Wythe Baylor: “Genl-John Robert Baylor of Texas” (3 of 5), 1900 December 25 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Biographical Materials: George Wythe Baylor: “Genl-John Robert Baylor of Texas” (4 of 5), 1900 December 25 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Biographical Materials: George Wythe Baylor: “Genl-John Robert Baylor of Texas” (5 of 5), 1900 December 25 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Biographical Materials: J.W. Baylor: “John Robert Baylor: 1822-1895”, 1906 May (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Biographical Materials: John George Walker, 1893 July 19-1984 June 2, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Biographical Materials: Charles Custis Rogers and Alice Ashmore Walker Rogers, 1902 September 2-1984 September 1 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Biographical Materials: George Wythe Baylor, 1915 October, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Biographical Materials: George Wythe Baylor Family, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Biographical Materials: Sophia Mary Baylor Walker, 1931 September 23-1984 September 1, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Biographical Materials: Harper Baylor Lee-Gillette, 1936 April 26-1966 April 6, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Biographical Materials: Robert Emmett Bledsoe Baylor, 1938 October 10-1966 March 27, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Biographical Materials: Carrington Family, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Clippings: General, 1893 July 6-1939 March 24 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Clippings: General, 1940 April 25-1975 August 13 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Clippings: General (1 of 3), undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Clippings: General (2 of 3), undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Clippings: General (3 of 3), undated (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1899-1900 January 13 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1900 January 20-1900-February 10 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1900 February 17-1900 August 11 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1900 August 13-1900 October 9 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1900 December 15-1900 December 22 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1901 February 23-1901 April 6 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1901 April 13-1901 April 20 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1901 April 27-1901 May 4 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1901 May 25-1901 August 3 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1901 August 10-1901 September 14 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1901 September 21-1901 November 16 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1901 November 23-1902 February 22 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1902 June 7-1902 November 1 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1902 November 8 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1906 January 6-1906 January 10 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Clippings: Newspaper Articles by George Wythe Baylor, 1930 January 24, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Clippings: Henry Weidner Baylor, 1853 September 15-1924 May 30, undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Clippings: Sophie E. Baylor, 1903 November 14-November 18 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Clippings: Addie Baylor Carrington, 1912-1984 September 26, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Clippings: George Wythe Baylor, 1913 November 9-1944 August, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Clippings: Eugene Wythe Baylor, 1918 January 8 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Clippings: Frances Courtney Baylor Barnum, 1920 October 15-16 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Clippings: John Robert Baylor, 1921 January-1990 March 17, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Clippings: John Roy Baylor and Jessie Kelso Baylor, 1949 July 6 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Clippings: Re: The Death of John Baylor, Jr., undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Manuscripts: Addie DeLeon Hamer Baylor (1 of 2), 1871 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Manuscripts: Addie DeLeon Hamer Baylor (2 of 2), 1871 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Manuscripts: R.C. Crane: Baylor County, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Manuscripts: Henry Weidner Baylor, 1929 May 28-1930 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Essays: Addie Baylor Carrington: “Chalk Bluff”, 1931 February (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Essays: Walker Keith Baylor: "Flag of John Robert Baylor", undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Poetry: Sue Baylor Adams, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Speeches: Walker Keith Baylor: “The Old Frontier: Events of Long Ago”, 1925 July (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Speeches: Walker Keith Baylor: “Memorial Address Delivered By W. K. Baylor, on Decoration Day at the Confederate Cemetery at San Antonio, Texas”, 1926 April 18 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Speeches: Walker Keith Baylor, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Certificates: Texas Veteran Association: John Robert Baylor and Emily “Emy” Jane Hanna Baylor, 1883 April 10 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Testimonials: Citizens of Uvalde County: Henry Weidner Baylor, 1891 February 27 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Real Estate Assessments: James Baylor Belger, undated (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Research Notes: Cyrus Alexander Baylor, 1957 September 26 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Research Notes: Baylor Massacre, 2007 June 27 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Books, 1791-1945; 5
  This series consists of books authored or collected by members of the Baylor and/or Carrington families, from the eighteenth to the twentieth centuries. There are a couple family Bibles containing birth, death, and marriage dates. Of particular note is a second edition of Thomas Jefferson's A Manual of Parliamentary Practice, from 1812, and George Wythe Baylor's copy of H.S. Thrall's History of Texas, which contains Baylor's marginalia regarding his own participation in the events described.
  - Bible: William Miller Baylor: Loose Items, 1791 September 25-1940 May 9 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Thomas Jefferson: A Manual of Parliamentary Practice, 1812 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - James Fenimore Cooper: The Water-Witch, 1830 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Bible: Duncan C. Carrington, undated (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Duncan C. Carrington: Loose Items, 1843 July 18-1948 January 30 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Bible: Duncan C. Carrington: Loose Items, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Bible: Laetitia B. Baylor, 1854 (Box 21 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Bible: Laetitia B. Baylor: Loose Items, 1859 July 12, 1927 October 31, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Hymnal, 1874 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - H.S. Thrall: A History of Texas: George Wythe Baylor, 1886 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Marietta Holley Allen: Sweet Cicely, 1887 (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Henry Wadsworth Longfellow: Early Poems, 1890 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - The Book of Common Prayer, 1890 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Hymnals, 1891 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Donald G. Mitchell: Dream-Life: A Fable of the Seasons, 1893 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Voltaire: Le Siècle De Louis XIV: Volume 1, 1897 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - George Madden Martin: Emy Lou: Her Book & Heart, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - The Book of Common Prayer and The Hymnal, 1903 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Washington Irving: The Sketch Book, 1908 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Orval W. Baylor and Henry B. Baylor: Baylor’s History of the Baylors, 1914 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Orval W. Baylor and Henry B. Baylor: Baylor’s History of the Baylors: Loose Items, 1914 (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 25)
  - Frances Hodgson Burnett: A Little Princess, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Alice L. Simrall: Margaret Baylor: An Interpretation, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Charles and Mary Lamb: Tales From Shakspeare, 1924 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Henrietta Stockley: Ranch Rhymes and Pasture Prattle, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Harry P. Hornby: Going Around, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - J. Montgomery Seaver: Allen Family Records, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - The Violin: How to Make It, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Bull Run to Bull Run by George Baylor, 1900 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Photographic Materials, 1849-1941; 6
  This series consists of photographs, negatives, and painting prints of members of the Baylor, Carrington, and Allen families. In addition to portraits, there are photographs of Baylor family reunions and the installing of the statue of R.E.B. Baylor at Baylor University.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Ambrotype; Daguerreotype; Photo negative; Photographic print
  - General, 1922, 1924, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - General (1 of 5), undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - General (2 of 5), undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - General (3 of 5), undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - General (4 of 5), undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - General (5 of 5), undated (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Portraits: John Baylor, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Portraits: George Baylor, 1919, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Portraits: Walker Baylor, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Portraits: John Walker Baylor, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Walker Keith Baylor, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Robert Emmett Bledsoe Baylor, undated (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Robert Emmett Bledsoe Baylor and Betsy Baylor Metcalf, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - John Robert Baylor, circa 1875, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Emily Jane Hanna Baylor, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - George Wythe Baylor (1 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - George Wythe Baylor (2 of 2), undated (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Tom Lea: George Wythe Baylor, 1965 (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 21)
  - Henry Weidner Baylor, circa 1854, circa 1900, 1929 June, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Henry Weidner Baylor, circa 1886 (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 22)
  - Henry Weidner Baylor, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Addie DeLeaon Hamer Baylor, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Susan Hamer Baylor Illg, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - John Roy and Jessie Kelso Baylor Family, 1895, 1905 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - John Roy and Jessie Kelso Baylor Family, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Harper Baylor Lee-Gillette, 1915 April 25 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - John Roy Baylor, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington Family, 1897-1936 December, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)